Guide to the George Washington University Publications collection, 1924-2017 RG0154
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Education, Series 5
  - Evaluation: processes and practices; selected papers from the Conference for the Evaluation of Instructional Materials, April 5-6, 1968, edited by Ginny Swisher, Carol Gross, Ellen Cramer., 1968-04-01; Series 5; 56 p. ill. 25 cm. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    The Special Education Instructional Materials Center at George Washington University, which sponsored this conference, changed its name to the Mid-Atlantic Region Special Education Materials Center in September 1968.; This center, one of 14 federally supported ones, was funded by the Bureau of Education for the Handicapped, United States Office of Education.; Bibliography: p. 17, 27-28.
  - Minimum competency testing: state approaches by Jimmie Covington., 1979-01-01; Series 5; 55 pages; 28 cm. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Competency testing: an overview and seven case studies by Robert A. Frahm., 1979-01-01; Series 5; 54 pages; 28 cm. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Competency based education: some educational, political and historical perspectives by Wayne Reilly., 1977-09-01; Series 5; 61 pages; 28 cm. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - A Study of the technical characteristics of the Regents Examinations: final report prepared by Isadore Goldberg; submitted by John T. Dailey, responsible investigator, Clinton A, Neyman, project director., 1967-06-01; Series 5; 96 pages; 28 cm (Box 3, Folder 33)
    Contract #C-0031.; Cover title.; Submitted to New York State Education Dept.
  - Viewpoints: contemporary educational issues: reports of Educational Staff Seminar programs, 1970-72., 1972; Series 5; 1 volume (various pagings); 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Viewpoints II: contemporary educational issues. Reports of Educational Staff Seminar programs., 1973; Series 5; ix, 268 pages 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Viewpoints III: contemporary educational issues: reports of Educational Staff Seminar programs, January-June 1974 compiled by Sharon Enright., Series 5; 1 volume (various pagings); 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Viewpoints IV: contemporary educational issues: reports of Educational Staff Seminar programs, July-December 1974 compiled by Sharon Enright., Series 5; 1 volume (various pagings); 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Viewpoints V: contemporary educational issues: reports of Educational Staff Seminar programs, January-June 1975 compiled by Sharon Enright., Series 5; 1 volume (various pagings); 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - California Educational Seminar by Stephen Weiner., 1979-01-01; Series 5; 36 leaves; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Cover title.; Work prepared as part of George Washington University's Institute for Educational Leadership.
  - Colorado Educational Seminar: [a report on the first year: 1973-74] by Sally Allen and Tom Neal., 1974-12-01; Series 5; 91 pages: illustrations; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Cover title.; Work prepared at George Washington University's Institute for Educational Leadership as part of its State Seminar Associates Program.
  - Connecticut Educational Seminar: [first year operation] by Ivan A. Backer., 1974-03-01; Series 5; 14, [2] leaves; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Illinois Educational Seminar: [report on the first year] by Robert A. Bunnell., 1974-09-01; Series 5; 13 leaves; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts educational seminar: [first year report submitted by Stephen Joel Trachtenberg and Craig Aramian]., 1974-09-01; Series 5; 18 pages; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    "The Associates program."; Cover title.; Work prepared at George Washington University's Institute for Educational Leadership as part its State Seminar Associates Program.
  - Michigan Education Seminars: annual report - 1977-78 Robert T. Cole; sponsored by the Associates Program - IEL in cooperation with the Educational Council of Michigan, Education Commission of the States., 1978-09-01; Series 5; 49 pages; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Work prepared by George Washington University's Institute for Educational Leadership as part of its State Seminar Associates Program.
  - Nebraska Educational Seminar, 1974-09-01; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Nevada Educational Seminar: [the first year: 1973-74] by Don W. Driggs., 1974-06-01; Series 5; 15, [1], iv pages; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Cover title.; Work prepared at George Washington University's Institute for Education Leadership.
  - The 1973 New Jersey Educational Seminar: a review of first year experiences by Paul L. Tractenberg., Series 5; 12 leaves; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Oregon Educational Seminar, 1976-07-01; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - The Rhode Island Educational Seminar: [a case study] by Elmer E. Cornwell, Jr., 1973-09-01; Series 5; 28 leaves; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - The Rhode Island Educational Seminar: [2nd annual report] by Elmer E. Cornwell, Jr., 1975-03-01; Series 5; 14 leaves; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Cover title.; Work prepared at George Washington University's Institute for Educational Leadership as part of its Associates Program.
  - The Rhode Island Educational Seminar: [third annual report] by Elmer E. Cornwell., 1976-01-01; Series 5; 12 leaves; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 16)
    Cover title.; Work prepared at George Washington Washington University's Institute for Educational Leadership as part of its State Seminar Associates Program.
  - The South Carolina Seminar: [first annual report] by Joy E. Sovde., 1975-11-01; Series 5; 7 leaves; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Cover title.; Work prepared at George Washington University's Institute for Educational Leadership as part of its States Seminar Associates Program.
  - Texas Educational Seminar: [a review of first year experiences] by Kenneth W. Tolo., 1975-03-01; Series 5; 1-25 [26-28] leaves; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Impressions of education in Australia: a report of the Educational Staff Seminar Study Mission, Oct. 1-19, 1975 edited by Harriet Goldberg., 1976-05-01; Series 5; ix, 201, A-13 pages; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Impressions of education in Great Britain: a report of the Educational Staff Seminar Study Mission, January 7-21, 1974 edited by George Lane., 1974-01-01; Series 5; v, 71, A1-A6 pages; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Impressions of education in Great Britain / edited by George Lane, 1974. -- Impressions of Soviet education / edited by Elizabeth Reisner, 1976. -- Impressions of education in Israel / edited by Judith Reed, 1976. -- Impressions of education in Australia / edited by Harriet Goldberg, 1975.
  - Impressions of education in Israel, a report of the educational staff seminar study tour, May 22-June 6, 1972. Edited by Gertrude Wright and Holly Knox., 1972-06-01; Series 5; 135 pages 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Impressions of education in Israel; a report of the Educational Staff Seminar Study Mission, November 15-30, 1973. Edited by Sharon Enright and John Schulz., 1973-11-01; Series 5; 159, A-1-A-8 pages 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Impressions of education in Israel: a report of the Educational Staff Seminar Study Mission, February 13-29, 1976 edited by Judith Reed., 1976-02-01; Series 5; xi, 123, A-6 pages; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Impressions of Education in Israel, 1976-05-01; Series 5 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Impressions of education in Japan: a report of the Educational Staff Seminar Study Tour, December 3-20, 1972 edited by Ellen Hoffman., 1972-12-01; Series 5; 79, x pages; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Impressions of education in Poland and Romania: a report of the Educational Staff Seminar Study Mission, October 7-19, 1976 edited by Gertrue Mitchell., 1976-10-01; Series 5; x, 166, A1-6 pages; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Impressions of education in the USSR; a report of the Educational Staff Seminar Study Tour, October 28-November 11, 1971. Edited by Sherry R. Arnstein and Ellen L. Sudow., 1971-11-01; Series 5; 62 pages 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Impressions of Soviet education, a second look: a report of the Educational Staff Seminar study tour, November 16-30, 1972 edited by George B. Lane., 1972-11-01; Series 5; 98, vi pages; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 26)
    An earlier report of a similar tour in 1971 entitled: Impressions of education in the USSR.
  - Impressions of Soviet education: a report of the Educational Staff Seminar Study Mission, November 14-18, 1974 edited by Elizabeth Reisner., 1975-08-01; Series 5; xi, 129, A1-A14 pages: illustrations; 28 cm. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Government funding policies and nontraditional programs by L. Richard Meeth., 1975-06-01; Series 5; 18 leaves; 28 cm (Box 4, Folder 28)
    Cover title.; Insert: 4 p. summary.; Includes bibliographical references.; Also issued online.
  - Federal programs supporting lifelong learning by Pam Christoffel., 1976-09-01; Series 5; 2, [2] leaves; 29 cm (Box 4, Folder 29)
    "Prepared as a service to participants in the Monthly Dialogue on Lifelong Learning, Sponsored by the Postsecondary Education Convening Authority ..."; Cover title.
  - Report of the P.E.C.A. Task Force on Lifelong Learning by Barbara Hodgkinson [and others]; Postsecondary Education Convening Authority, Institute for Educational Leadership., 1977-02-01; Series 5; [80] pages in various pagings; 23 cm (Box 4, Folder 30)
    Work supported by a grant from HEW's Fund for the Improvement of Postsecondary Education to IEL's Postsecondary Education Convening Authority.
  - Education and its environment in the United States and overseas; a tentative selective checklist of books and articles, compiled by Henry Grattan Doyle [higher education specialist]., 1959; Series 5; iii, 207, iii pages 27 cm (Box 4, Folder 31)
    Cover title.; In Faculty Collection.
- Education Policy, Series 6
  - The Faculty as Teachers: A Perspective on Evaluation, 1971-09-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - College Grading Practices: An Overview, 1971-03-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Resources on Academic Bargaining and Governance, 1974-07-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - The Professor's Role in a Changing Society, 1971-06-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Professional Problems: Preparations for a Career in College Teaching, 1970-04-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Research on College Teaching, 1970-11-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Preparing College Teachers, 1970-08-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Campus Governance, 1971-07-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Planning Techniques for University Management, 1970; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Corporate Planning Models for University Management, 1970-10-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A Survery of the Resources in the Washington Area for the Training of School Administrators, 1952-06-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Perspectives on Federal Educational Policy: An Informal Colloquium, 1976-08-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Essays on Federal Education Policy, 1975-05-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Look At Federal Education Policy: Report on the Washington Policy Seminar for Career Educators, 1977-04-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Financing Higher Education, 1971-03-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Planning for Educational Development in a Planning, Programming, Budgeting System, 1968; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Reform in the State Budgeting of Postsecondary Education, 1976-06-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Public Spending for Higher Education, 1970, 1965-02-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Incentive Grant Approach in Higher Education: A 15-Year Record, 1976-03-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Recurring Themes in Educational Finance in the History of Washington D.C. 1804-1982, 1982-04-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - School Finance Patterns in the South: Reform Efforts, Current Problems and Prospects fro the Future, 1979-01-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Consortia in American Higher Education, 1970-11-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Year-Round Operations in American Universities, 1970; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Brown Decision 25 Years Later: Indicators of Desegregation and Equal Educational Opportunity, 1979-05-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Brown v. Board of Education: 25 Years Toward Equal Educational Opportunity, 1979-02-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - How to increase your verbal skills in high school courses by Jane Burkhardt, Jean McNelis, E. Lakin Phillips., 1970; Series 6; 172, [8] pages; 28 cm (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - A Model Training Project Development and Administration of Continuing Education for Women Programs, 1977-08-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Institutional Analysis of Sex Discrimination, 1973-06-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - The Status of Academic Women, 1971-04-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Handbook on How To End Sexism in your Schools, 1976-05-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Hierarchy, Power, and Women in Educational Policy Making, 1976-05-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Women in Educational Leadership: An Open Letter to State Legislators, 1976-05-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Development and Administration of Continuting Education for Women 1964-1974, Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - A Handbook for Administrators of Continuing Education for Women Programs, 1977-05-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - The Design and Evaluation of Vocational Technical Education Curricula Through Functional Job Analysis, 1968-08-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Development of a Curriculum and Materials for Teaching Basic Vocational Talents, 1966-04-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Title III and the World of Work, 1972; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Reorienting Vocational Education: Policy Papers in Human Resources and Industrial Relations, 1968-05-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Relevance Revisited: Curriculum Development in the Humanities - Service, Learning and Industrial Development, 1977; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Relevance Revisited: Curriculum Development in the Humanities - Administrative Strategies for Curriculum Change, 1977; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Relevance Revisited: Curriculum Development in the Humanities - Humanists and Policy Studies, 1977; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Relevance Revisited: Curriculum Development in the Humanities - Local Studies and Experiential Learning, 1977; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Reforming Undergraduate Curriculum: Problems and Proposals, 1971-03-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - College Credit for Off-Credit Study, 1971-03-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Student Initiated Changes in the Academic Curriculum, 1972-07-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - The Classical Education, 1977; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Toward Increasing the Social Relevance of the Contemporary University, 1969-08-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Development of a Curricum and Materials for Teaching Basic Vocational Talents, 1967-07-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - What is Humanistic Education?: Report of a Conference of the Dilthey Society of George Washington University, 1973-10-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Humanities, Education, and Working: Project Quill at George Washington University, 1980; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Public Humanities: An Old Role in Contemporary Perspective, 1984; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Approaches to State Licensing of Private Degree-Granting Institutions, 1975-11-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Structural Innovations in Higher Education to Meet Social Needs, 1970-12-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Keystone Workshop for State Licensing/Approving Officials, 1976-10-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Working Conference for State Licensing Officials, 1975-07-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Shaping of Professional Subcultures: A Study of Student Groups From Five Professions, 1960s; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Behavioral Factors in Dental School Design, 1966-12-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Personality Variables and Career Decisions: A Pilot Study of Law and Social Work Students, 1966-02-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Assessing Student Performance in College, 1970-05-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - The Student in Graduate School, 1972-01-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - A Matter of Degree: The Setting for Contemporary Master's Programs, 1973-01-01; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Education in the 1970's, 1977; Series 6 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ERIC/Higher Education Publication List 1968-1974, 1974-07-01; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ERICbyHigher education publications list, 1968-1976., 1976-02-01; Series 6; v, 45 pages; 23 cm (Box 2, Folder 1)
    "This publication was prepared pursuant to a contract with the national Institute of Education, U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare."; Includes subject, author, and title indexes.
  - ERIC/Higher Education Publication List 1972-1978, 1978-03-01; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Directory of higher education programs and faculty., 1982-03-01; Series 6; volume; 28 cm. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Lst.-2nd edition compiled by Marilyn Shorr; 3rd. edition- by Marilyn Shorr and Lisa Hoogstra.
  - Compendum Series of Current Research, Programs and Proposals: Governance, 1970-05-01; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The crisis of purpose: definition and uses of institutional goals., 1970-05-01; Series 6; 13 pages 28 cm. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 11-13).
  - Open Admissions in Higher Education, 1971-06-01; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - The Experimental Subcollege, 1971-06-01; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Accountability in higher education., 1972-02-01; Series 6; v, 58 pages 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 51-58).
  - Collective bargaining on campus Carol. H. Shulman; prepared by ERIC Clearinghouse on Higher Education, George Washington University., 1972-03-01; Series 6; 45 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 51-58).; Also available online from the ERIC website.
  - State aid to private higher education by Carol Herrnstadt Shulman., 1972-06-01; Series 6; v, 38 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Prepared by the ERIC Clearinghouse on Higher Education, George Washington University.; Includes bibliographical references.; Also available online.
  - The numbers 2 access problem: transfer to the upper division by Warren W. Willingham., 1972-07-01; Series 6; 60 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Prepared by the ERIC Clearinghouse on Higher Education.; Includes bibliographical references (pages 51-60).
  - Who benefits from higher education--and who should pay? [By] Howard R. Bowen [and] Paul Servelle. Prepared by the ERIC Clearinghouse on Higher Education, George Washington University., 1972-08-01; Series 6; 49 pages 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 41-49).
  - A current perspective on accreditation by Frank G. Dickey and Jerry W. Miller., 1972-11-01; Series 6; 68 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 61-68).; Also issued online through the ERIC website.; Prepared pursuant to a contract with the Office of Education, U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare.
  - Strategies for improving college teaching., 1972-12-01; Series 6; 51 pages 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 45-51).
  - The impact of the academic revolution on faculty careers [by] D.W. Light, Jr., L.R. Marsden, [and] T.C. Corl., 1973-02-01; Series 6; 73 pages 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 69-73).
  - Productivity: burden of success by William Toombs., 1973-05-01; Series 6; 55 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 45-55).
  - University-city relations: from coexistence to cooperation by Bernard H. Ross., 1973; Series 6; 38 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The integration of learning and earning: cooperative education and nontraditional study by K. Patricia Cross., 1973; Series 6; 65 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 58-65).; Also issued online through the ERIC website.; Prepared pursuant to a contract with the National Institute of Education, U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare.
  - Comparative higher education by Philip G. Altbach., 1973; Series 6; 81 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 48-81).
  - Goals for higher education: definitions and directions by David A. Trivett., 1973; Series 6; 61 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    "Prepared by the ERIC Clearinghouse on Higher Education, the George Washington University."; Includes bibliographical references (pages 56-61).; Also issued online through the ERIC website.; Prepared pursuant to a contract with the National Institute of Education, U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.
  - Student discipline systems in higher education by Stanford Cazier., 1973; Series 6; 47 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 42-47).; Also issued online through the ERIC website.; Prepared pursuant to a contract with the National Institute of Education, U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.
  - Employment of nontenured faculty: some implications of Roth and Sindermann by Carol Herrnstadt Shulman., 1973; Series 6; 68 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 23-25).
  - Urban Internships in Higher Education, 1973; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The changing profile of college students by Robert H. Fenske and Craig S. Scott., 1973; Series 6; 77 pages; 22 cm. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    "Prepared by the ERIC Clearinghouse on Higher Education, the George Washington University."; Includes bibliographical references (pages 51-56).
  - The "Benefits Crisis" in higher education by Oscar T. Lenning., 1974; Series 6; 62 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 42-52).; Also available online from the ERIC website.
  - Proprietary schools and postsecondary education David A. Trivett; prepared by the ERIC Clearinghouse on Higher Education, the George Washington University., 1974; Series 6; 54 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 48-54).
  - How much change for a dollar?: a look at Title III by Harold L. Hodgkinson., 1974; Series 6; 53 pages: illustrations; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    "Prepared by the ERIC Clearinghouse on Higher Education, the George Washington University, Washington, D.C."; Includes bibliographical references (pages 51-53).
  - Higher education and the steady state Larry L. Leslie and Howard F. Miller, Jr.; prepared by the ERIC Clearinghouse on Higher Education, the George Washington University, Washington, D.C., 1974; Series 6; 58 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 51-58).; Prepared pursuant to a contract with the National Institute of Education, U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare.
  - The personalized system of instruction: an educational alternative by Robert S. Ruskin., 1974; Series 6; 44 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 39-44).; Prepared pursuant to a contract with the National Institute of Education, U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.
  - Faculty workload: facts, myths and commentary by Harold E. Yuker., 1974; Series 6; 62 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 55-62).
  - Time shortened degrees Charles W. Meinert; prepared by the ERIC Clearinghouse on Higher Education, George Washington University., 1974; Series 6; 76 pages; 23 cm. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Includes bibliographical references (pages 69-76).; Prepared pursuant with a contract with the National Institute of Education, U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.